Let's let's do a quick uh round of
intros. So, Adam, you want to introduce
yourself first?
>> Yeah. My name is Adam Dish. I manage the
application security team at a company
called Commerce, formerly Big Commerce.
Think of Shopify competitor.
That's how you get it.
>> Cool. Yep. And I'm over at Dryrun
Security. Um you know, Amir said that
security sucks with AI, but that's
actually not true. Uh not if you're
using dry run security.
>> Okay, there you go.
>> Okay. Hey. Um, here here is the the
landscape as we see it and the the facts
on the field. Um, the the blue lines in
the back are kind of the amount of code
that's getting written year-over-year
and that's continuing uh to grow in
scale and uh, you know, grab several
different data sources here, but about a
doubling in the last two and a half
years roughly. Uh, does anybody think
that this is going to slow down or this
is going to get get lower, right? No.
like like every every thing you read uh
in the next 5 years this is going to
triple uh quadruple uh something
something like that. Um at the same time
um we're seeing the markers for what we
call like classic risks. So think about
like SQL injection cross-ite scripting
kind of the OASP top 10 like we were
talking about. That's actually on the
decline and and like why why is that?
And then at the same time we're seeing
an increase in what we have kind of
labeled here as contextual risk. Uh but
this is like the proxy for that is like
authorization and logic. Now that's a
little bit hard to discern because you
have to actually pull in bug bounty data
to to help figure this out. Um because
most uh tools like sneak and sim and
code all that sort of stuff like they
can't figure out authorization and logic
issues. That's just not in their
purview. Um so but but somewhere about
mid midlast year kind of there's an
inversion uh where like you know AI
actually we we believe AI will write
more secure code in the sense of like
less classical risk stuff will be
presented in it because guess what it
knows how to learn patterns u but more
contextual risk business logic
authorization things like that uh will
continue to be on the rise because uh
just like we said earlier like humans
make mistakes AI plus humans will make
mistakes like that is that is pretty
much given So this is the the landscape
that we see at over at dry run security
and um Adam you want to talk about the
setup of like uh agents using uh credit
cards.
>> Yeah. So if anyone was paying attention
to Open AI this afternoon you might have
seen a small article drop around aentic
checkout. Perfect timing for this talk
honestly. So we'll begin with a
question. How many of you use AI to ask
questions instead of Google more on a
day-to-day basis?
the entire audience. Perfect. How many
of you would trust trust AI to make a
purchase on your behalf?
One person.
So that's essentially where the future
of commerce is going. So e-commerce is
now in this new space age of utilizing
artificial intelligence to help make
purchasing decisions. Um, and a lot of
this comes down to
MCP servers, more specifically having
access to catalog metadata of an
e-commerce website, whether or not it's
eBay, Etsy, your traditional mom and pop
Lego store down the street or your, you
know, your comic book store that happens
to have their catalog online. So,
they're getting access to metadata
associated with your catalog. You're
then using AI to say, "Hey, I want to
find a new t-shirt in this size, in this
color range, within this price range."
It will then search its metadata, the
catalog of metadata, and present you
with some options. So, luckily, there's
still some human in the middleesque
aspects associated with it. But you then
basically say, I want to purchase, I
want to select this product. It will
then pro provide you some more details.
you say buy and then it will literally
buy that product on your behalf and then
you'll all of a sudden receive an order
notification email in your inbox. Um, so
the real question there is
why does this essentially matter, right?
So as you've seen open AAI, it's now
completely available on chat GPT with
any Etsy storefront.
Um, you got catalog information exposed.
How can that potentially ruin your day
with your AI agent that you happen to e
either running locally or within your
browser? and the fact that because all
everyone is now using AI on a more
day-to-day basis for general questions
instead of Google, you're getting more
trust and more familiarity with it,
which means it's going to grow even
further and even quicker. So, it's a
scaling risk, right? And it's not just a
security risk, you also have the privacy
and fraud aspect associated with it as
well as it continues to grow.
And that fraud risk is only going to
compound as the holiday season comes.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
how in the battle with e-commerce or
bots in general, we've always said bots
bad block bot.
So things like recapture,
laughs, blocking traffic from even
hitting your your websites to say to not
skew analytical information, to not
scrape your data, to prevent potentially
fraudulent transactions from coming
through through an automated process for
credit card scamming or
essentially carding attacks. So how do
we differentiate different differentiate
a good bot from a bad bot? Luckily, our
good folks at Cloudflare are paving the
way for this specifically with
cryptographic signatures associated with
the with the AI bot and OpenAI is kind
of leading the effort for that as well
with with Cloudflare. There's an
article. It was posted five days ago.
Read it.
>> Awesome. Awesome.
>> Um, so real world scenario, right? This
is kind of kind of explained briefly,
but you know, you log into your agent.
You say, "Hey, find me this product.
It adds it queries all the MCP servers
that it has access to, whether or not
it's Etsy, Shopify, Commerce, eBay."
Probably fairly soon, I'm sure, we'll
get an an email from eBay saying, "We
have MCP. Congratulations. Consume it."
Um, and then it will rank all that
information based off of the metadata
that it has access to. So reviews
associated with the products, the
descriptions, meta keywords, etc. And
then it will provide you with that with
that output into your agent to say here
are the best options that I found for
you based off of the prompt that you
gave me.
We're we're going to get there with OASP
10. Um and then you basically say select
purchase, confirm the transaction, and
you're done. So that means you're giving
your agent credit card information,
potentially PayPal information, you're
giving it PII with your shipping
information. So there's also a lot of
session handling that needs to be
carefully articulated within that
process.
>> That's great.
So I'll kind of build those out real
quick. So yeah, so what what do you see
as like the main threats that we we have
to face, right? like there's the um
there's the the like all the assets that
like can be you know interacted with
there right
>> so one of the main assets and this is
something that we've proven internally
is it's fairly easy to get prompt
injection through catalog information of
a product if your agent is misconfigured
i.e If you're running it in yellow mode,
for example, you can get RCE. You're
going to get prompt injection. So there
has to be very careful input and output
handling and formatting of that data
that you're passing through the MCP
server to say, hey, this is accurate
information. And honestly, the Agentic
Commerce protocol that OpenAI just
announced
earlier this afternoon is actually a
great way to go about it because it's
going to be a standardized process.
hopefully. Um, and then you also have
all the all the different actors that
can be part of this. You're going to
have your fraud rings that will pop up
during the holiday season selling
products that are priced too good to be
true. So, they're going to be within
your price range. You're like, "Oh, that
might be good." Because how many of us
have purchased something on Amazon or
eBay or name your third party
marketplace here and have potentially
and have been scammed out of a product
before?
>> Yeah.
>> Yep. It's it's happened to almost
everyone and it's going to and this is
just going to be another component of
that. So you have to have fraud controls
in place to dictate what
catalog information potentially gets
surfaced to the MCP server to be
provided to agents. And that's a
conversation that hasn't happened in a
in a lot of places yet. Probably
happening internally, but nothing's been
shared.
>> Okay. So, this is the the uh OASP top 10
for um LLM apps. And we're going to
focus on a few of those in our in our
talk, but you can kind of see how they
follow um a a different uh type of of
thinking and it's a different type of
risk vectors than kind of we've been
used to for the majority of our um you
know, of our lives in security, right?
Feels like appsc is always kind of the
same the same thing, right? Like
crossite scripting, SQL injection,
right? I I I feel like I dream about
that in my sleep now and that's that
feels so weird. But like um but this is
this is where we're we're heading and
this is the type of uh risks that are
continuing we're continuing to face. So
um we're we focused on four uh key areas
that we want to talk about on this. So
we're going to talk about prompt
injection. We're going to talk about
excessive agency. Um we're going to talk
about unbounded uh consumption and uh
sensitive uh information disclosure kind
of we you know kind of is woven
throughout all that. So um and we're
going to talk about that in the the you
know realm of of uh of having agents do
all your your checkout and and uh and
purchasing. Uh and then you know all the
normal stuff still does apply. It is
still relevant. U but but we're kind of
hitting the uh the bigger stuff here.
So, all right. Um, prompt prompt
injection. Um, like Adam was mentioning,
like this can get put inside of
cataloges, but you see it in like
product descriptions, uh, uh, merchant
notes. Um, is there anything that you're
super concerned about about this and,
you know, like like the high high issues
for you?
>> So, in terms of pro prompt injection
specifically for agentic checkout, a lot
of it's going to be driven through mer
essentially merchant supplied input with
their with their catalog information. So
it's not so it's going to be more of a
third party risk than necessarily a
first party risk. Um it'd be very
similar to say using
Vibe coding to build a new web app and
it potentially installing a malicious
dependency. Um it's that's still a third
party risk, not necessarily a prompt
injection risk, but that third party
risk still exists. But in this case,
prompt injection in in the sense of
agent checkout is a third party risk,
not a first party risk. And you got to
make sure that you have the safeguards
in place to prevent it from happening.
>> Cool. What about like um user reviews
and stuff like that? Like how do those
get treated in the in the catalog?
>> It's all all metadata.
>> It all gets kind of merged in there,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Um is anybody dealing with this kind of
stuff right now? Like are you building
LLM apps and you're kind of worried
about this level of stuff? Got a couple
hands. One, two, three, four, five, six.
Okay. Yep. Cool.
All right. um excessive agency. You
know, now I can be like, "Oh, no. It's
like the bot went bad and I purchased
all these packages on my front door."
Right. That's the That's That was the
joke. That's it. That's where we are on
that. Okay. All right. Adam.
>> Um so for excessive agency, who all saw
the uh Open AI bug report about their
MCP server exposing a bunch of Gmail
records?
Exact same thing is that's what this is
in this case. Excessive agency. you're
you're essentially giving your agent too
many permissions to access outside
resources, right? So, this is all about
agent configuration or or essentially
tool configuration whether or not it's
an internal like tool that AI driven
solution that you're running in-house
for your company like make IO or or
anything else that you might be running
or whe you know Slack or Atlassian or
internal Atlassian services as well.
Excessive agency is essentially just
making sure that
you have fine grain per fine grained
permissions associated within all the
tasks that you have integrated within
your AI solution to make sure that it
can't potentially steal all your Gmail
records and send them off to SAM at
Cloudflare to get data populated within
some black market website. Right? So
just be careful about configurations.
consult legal and privacy if you have
any questions about potential risks
around leaking potentially confidential
information. Yeah.
And then uh un unbounded consumption. Um
you know this looks like you know we're
we're an AI uh company delivering
services for um you know our our
customers. And so we're even consumed
with this or concerned at this uh
runaway consumption where you can have
um you know loops go go bad or you can
have um uh searches get too aggressive
and try to go into agentic mode looking
at a bunch of different code. Um Adam,
how are you uh dealing with this or how
are you
>> A lot of it is rate limiting um and then
monitoring essentially. So if anyone's
familiar with like GraphQL, how you can
add complexity scores to it. Kind of try
to do something similar with within your
actual calls that that you're making
through your through your agents that
are might potentially be GraphQL API
driven. Those complexity scores will
make a huge difference in making sure
that you're not going to consume as many
tokens as you were initially expecting
to drive up additional costs. But really
rate limiting rate limiting is going to
be your best friend for absolutely
everything you do any for anything API
related which honestly when you're
talking about a commerce it's all API
driven in the back end. It's just yeah
>> you have a robot helping you along the
way.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
And then uh this is specifically for
catalog spoofing and price manipulation.
Um we have a couple of uh vectors and
controls here that you're looking at.
>> Yeah. And what this really boils down to
is don't fully trust a third party
input. Um when you have fraud fraud in
play, you you got to make necessary
decisions on what data you're
potentially going to allow to be
interfaced with your agents. whether or
not that for example with with Etsy and
OpenAI,
how do they determine if like if I spin
up a new Etsy shop tonight and start
selling candles, is that instantly going
to be available on Open AI through JG
GPT or are they going to have some form
of waiting period to make sure that I'm
not a malicious actor trying to prompt
inject, you know, Sam's agent or James'
agent or whatever, right? Mhm.
>> So it's we don't know what their
decision- making is and every company's
going to have their own decision-m when
it comes to how they're going to combat
fraud and what their acceptable risks
are. So it's really just having a form
of acceptable risk that satisfies both
legal and compliance.
>> Yeah.
Well, we do have a couple tips here on
privacy and compliance. You may just
kind of build I'll build these out here
real quick for us. Um yeah, so
really it's starting any new project. Um
make sure all risks and security aspects
are accounted for. Um loop in legal and
compliance as necessary especially
depending on the frameworks that you're
going to be dealing with whether or not
that's PCI, GDPR, HIPPA, Fed ramp. um
make just essentially make sure that
your project is
built from the ground up with a security
architecture in place but also with a
legal and compliance aspect as well if
you're dealing with any kind of
compliance frameworks that might be
impacted
>> and and um we think about this like so
we kind of said like hey there's context
based risk then there's like pattern
based risk and like how does uh how do
we think about that and so Um at at uh
dry run security we think about
contextual security analysis as looking
at the surface, the language, the
intent, the design and the environment.
Um it allows us to reason about
authorization, data flows, side effects.
Um and each of our agents can spit up s
sub aents to look for uh additional like
truths about the system as it's trying
to build out the context of knowing uh
what's going on. So, um it allows us to
look um at for flaws that you couldn't
find before with traditional tools like
uh insecure direct object reference or
uh or even some SSRFs can be really
difficult to detect. Um and and you're
look we're looking for context level
vulnerabilities. So, uh some of the
things that are like available like in
the OASP LLM uh uh top 10 there is also
fair game. So we um we haven't released
all the data on this but we expect to do
that pretty uh pretty soon. Uh but we
took dry run security and compared it to
some other uh AI native SAS tools to
sneak sim grep uh github advanced
security codeql and then we just ran
through uh individual commits on each of
these um and we're trying to like just
show off like hey here's here's what we
would do like you know have prompt
injection or uh sensitive information
disclosure and kind of work our way
through and then just score which ones
we could find and which ones we couldn't
find. Um and we did we did uh really
really well on this. We had we had run a
similar experiment on this in April just
like looking against like uh pattern
matching tools and like looking for like
the cross-ite scripting into SQL
injection. Um and we saw that that uh
kind of the context driven approach was
like two or three times better than the
than the pattern based approach. Um but
here all the all the threat vectors are
all context based. So it's like it sort
of feels like you're receding the field
unfairly there. But um that that is is
definitely the case that there is a new
class of tools that are kind of rising
up at this moment. Uh because uh if
you're building LLM based apps, if
you're having MCP servers or if you're
like uh providing even data that's going
to be working with those like if you're
producing the catalogs or the uh other
components to uh be part of that system,
you need you need to be watching out for
this this level of risk and that's uh
we're kind of seeing that be important.
So um there's also uh we also in our
conversation uh as we're kind of
building this out we're also discussing
like what kind of controls can we put in
place uh for like runtime. So because
driving security we're only from like
you know code getting written to like
build time but then like well how do you
do it as you're as you're going forward
with you know monitoring observability
and so so yeah um a lot of the runtime
controls let's just are really going to
be boiled down to
scopes and and
human middle controls essentially um
making sure that any sensitive action
that your agent is take that taking
place for you has some form of approval
associated with it. Whether or not
that's sending an email, completing a
purchase, even potentially writing a new
Jurro ticket depending on, you know, the
s the data sensit data sensitivity
classification associated with it.
Otherwise, you know, multiffactor
authentication, correct API scopes, um,
or even a good WFT does a lot. There's
actually a lot of companies out there
that are in the process of building AI
ccentric WS. Um whether or not from
startups, I'm sure Cloudflare has
something. I haven't seen it. Um but
even like Google with their Vertex AI
and their model armor has a solution as
well. Um and then just consistent
monitoring and alerting. You know, the
more red blinky lights the better to say
red alert, red alert, please check me
out. Make sure this is okay. Um, just
build context, build alerting, implement
as many security controls that you would
for your typical infrastructure stack or
even your web application stack to
basically monitor monitor and maintain
and block those lowhanging fruit items
that you that you probably deal with on
a day-to-day basis that you just want to
make sure that potentially won't impact
you.
>> Okay. So, we have we have a few like
take-home ideas here for you, like your
your agents need guardrails, uh context
uh beats patterns for uh for AI type
bugs. Um I thought I thought we you
shared a lot of really good stuff around
like security fraud uh and how like and
how uh you got to deal with like fraud
and privacy and GRC kind of early early
on in your in your build process.
>> Um
Yep. See here. And then uh okay, we have
a we have a few references for you. So,
uh, how do you want to talk through your
yours here and I'll I'll mention mine.
>> Um, yeah, in short, Agent Commerce is
here. It's going to grow even further.
Um, PayPal is getting a dentic payments
into play and accessing catalog
information as well as Open AI. Um,
and and really it's it's going to be the
future for shopping in in some aspect.
Whether or not the trust level is going
to be there in a month or in a year,
that's to be seen. But it's going to
it's unfortunately going to be the
future and it's going to be here sooner
than we all expected. We're all probably
in a next 6 months to a year, every
single one of us will say, "Yes, we've
made a purchase using chat GPT or Gemini
or Perplexity or name your flavor of
agent here." And that that's the that's
the world we'll be in. And I'm sure
Amazon will have an AI shopping agent
for you soon, too.
>> I'm ready for Black Friday right now.
Ready? Well, that that and that last one
uh we found that was today, right? That
came out today.
>> Yeah. Aentic commerce uh protocol. And
then uh yeah, I put a driver in security
like a report to the SAS accuracy thing
if you're interested in that as well. Um
okay, so do we have time for questions
or how are we doing? Yeah, we have time.